[
    {
        "question":"which variable we store in global scope?",
        "option1":"var",
        "option2":"let",
        "option3":"const",
        "option4":"int",
        "ans":1                                                                                                
        
    },
    {
        "question":"which one is equality operator??",
        "option1":"==",
        "option2":"===",
        "option3":"=",
        "option4":"None of the above",
        "ans":1
    },
    {
        "question":"what is the return type of array",
        "option1":"function",
        "option2":"object",
        "option3":"array",
        "option4":"string",
        "ans":2
    },
    {
        "question":"by using which ,method we can insert the array element at the end",
        "option1":"push",
        "option2":"pop",
        "option3":"shift",
        "option4":"unshift",
        "ans":1
    },
    {
        "question":"how many types of scope we have in js?",
        "option1":"global scope",
        "option2":"script scope",
        "option3":"local scope",
        "option4":"All Of The above",
        "ans":4
    },
    {
       "question":"how to handle promise?",
        "option1":"then and catch",
        "option2":"then and finally",
        "option3":"try and finally",
        "option4":"try,catch and finally",
        "ans":4 
    },
    {
        "question":"which operator is mandatory to perform async function ?",
        "option1":"spread operator",
        "option2":"equality operator",
        "option3":"await operator",
        "option4":"None of the above",
        "ans":3
    },
    {
"question":"What will be the output of the following code  print(typeof(NaN));",
"option1":"Object",
"option2":"Number",
"option3":"String",
"option4":"None of the above",
"ans":2
    },
    {
        "question":"When an operatorâ€™s value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is:",
         "option1":"Boolean",
         "option2":"Undefined",
        "option3":"Object",
        "option4":"Integer",
        "ans":3
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following are closures in Javascript?",
        "option1":"Variable",
        "option2":"Function",
       "option3":"Objects",
       "option4":"All Of The above",
       "ans":4
    }
]